midamericanenergy.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy

## About MidAmerican Energy's Privacy Statement

Berkshire Hathaway Energy knows how important it is to protect the information provided by our customers and visitors to our website or obtained through cookies. It is Berkshire Hathaway Energy's policy to safeguard and protect all personal information collected from Berkshire Hathaway Energy's website and to keep such information confidential. This policy applies to all information collected or submitted on our website.

Berkshire Hathaway Energy's Web server recognizes the domain name and email address, when provided, of each customer and visitor to our site.

Berkshire Hathaway Energy uses the information obtained from our website to better understand and serve our customers by:

  * improving the content of our Web pages;
  * customizing the content and/or layout of our pages for customers and visitors;
  * notifying persons about updates to Berkshire Hathaway Energy's website; and
  * contacting customers and visitors to respond to their questions and fulfill their requests for more information.

Except as provided below, Berkshire Hathaway Energy does not share this information with outside parties unless such disclosure is required by law.

In order to secure and safeguard the information collected on Berkshire Hathaway Energy's website, including restricting unauthorized access, maintaining data accuracy, and ensuring the appropriate use of information, Berkshire Hathaway Energy has designed and instituted appropriate physical, electronic and administrative procedures. While Berkshire Hathaway Energy believes these procedures are adequate, Berkshire Hathaway Energy cannot guarantee their absolute performance.

Berkshire Hathaway Energy and its third-party service providers collect IP addresses and related information such as: originating and destination information; date and time stamps of communications; indicators of the type of operating system; hypertext protocol headers; application client and server banners; and information about the type of request, such as whether it is requesting or sending data. Berkshire Hathaway Energy and its third-party service providers organize and analyze these types of information to support internal operations, including maintaining functionality of websites and diagnosing website issues, analyzing trends, providing more efficient service, maintaining and/or enhancing security for users and the websites, producing traffic volume statistics, and making the websites and our infrastructure more useful and secure. In an effort to protect the security of Berkshire Hathaway Energy’s critical infrastructure, any use of a website or information relating to such use (as described above) may be monitored and disclosed to federal authorities or agencies without further notice to you.

Berkshire Hathaway Energy uses email addresses, when provided, to answer the email we receive and fulfill your requests. If you do not wish to receive email regarding information about Berkshire Hathaway Energy, or information about Berkshire Hathaway Energy's products and services, email us at [info@midamerican.com](mailto:info@midamerican.com).

### Disclosure Statement – Use of Cookies

Berkshire Hathaway Energy's website utilizes cookies to provide visitors to our website a more convenient and enjoyable experience. Berkshire Hathaway Energy does not collect personal information without our customers' or visitors' knowledge, nor does Berkshire Hathaway Energy resell or distribute any data about the customers or visitors who access our website.

If you have questions about Berkshire Hathaway Energy's Privacy Policy, email us at [info@midamerican.com](mailto:info@midamerican.com).
